[Music]
okay manic this should be all of it
remember to get the money back for the
delivery and whatever you do be careful
be careful but what for ain't I just
dropping off clothes what could possibly
be dangerous about that unless I'm
delivering in the hood
while I didn't want to scare you but
[__] it there's this huge man in a brown
[__] colored suit staking out our
laundromat lately three of our employees
have been attacked and dragged into a
back alley by him he didn't beat them up
or anything just took the clothes and
ran
a big guy in brown clothes up why does
that sound so familiar
well thanks for the heads up boss I'll
try and be careful
this is so exciting I can't wait to see
the looks on Sonic and Sonia's faces
when I get my first paycheck I'll
finally be the talk at the dinner table
for sure no more having to hear this or
that about bartlebby
my brother's millionaire boyfriend
I wonder how long it'll be before I'm a
millionaire
ha ha ha all right 12 bucks saved yet
again
just another day for Farrell the
greatest Eve whoever lived
manic my boy what are you doing here
and why do you have my clean laundry
clenched in your hand
oh I get it you stole it from the
laundry man on the way here before I did
you crazy [__] I see I taught you well
but I didn't teach you all I know cause
as you can see I just schooled your ass
feral no Say It Isn't So you've been the
one stealing from the town laundromat
this whole time
[Music]
well well well looks like you figured it
all out what do you want a kiss on the
behind
Ferrell you have to give me those
clothes back
my job is on the line here
I'll be taking these and I'll take what
you got as well
give me your Apple Red Sneakers right
now
no way these kicks are mine old man they
wouldn't even fit you
and you have to be [__] if you think
I'm letting you have those clothes
foreign
you do not raise your voice at me my boy
shut up you are not my daddy anymore you
smelly fat [__] oh so you're an employee
who takes orders now what the [__]
joke never in my wildest dreams were the
ones great Manic the Hedgehog resort to
getting a job to earn some coins up in
this [__]
at least I'm doing something with my
life unlike you
you want to say that again my boy as a
matter of fact I do eurotun stink bug
looking ass look at you hiding in
Alleyways like a rat you're the one
who's a joke feral
I I don't care what people think of me
and I have no intention on paying for
something I already own [__]
are you saying those are your clothes
hahaha oh manic surely the ways of the
thief haven't left you that much
[Music]
you know as well as I do why I put this
Alleyway on the address line dumb [__]
it's so they can't track my ass down and
sue me I've done this eight times
already wearing eight different
disguises eight different names
at that laundromat you're working now
and they haven't caught wind of me yet
so you really were the piece of crap my
boss warned me about
perhaps but who cares I was ready to go
live in a different alley anyway
good luck catching me then fool
don't even try to get up again manic
unless you want this day to be your last
upon this feeble Earth
what you want proof
oh did Papa make this dinky again
there now don't you see the difference
in our current power levels you don't
poop your head I recommend you go home
you've already let your Mentor down once
do not let it happen again
and you just let him get away with doing
you in like that come on man where's
your balls
what was I supposed to do steal them
back from him in broad daylight they
were like three people next to that
alleyway
at least you wouldn't have taken it like
a [__] easy for you to say Knox you've
never been on the opposite end up feral
the master Thief stripe and nasty pimple
laced buttcrack
Manuka I'm only going to say this once
because it's Taco Tuesday and I have to
run home soon
but I think it's time for you to
remember your own strengths
we awaken the animal inside you and go
get those gosh dang clothes back
the animal inside me
hell yeah [__] the master thief
of days gone by he's still there waiting
to explode out like a diarrhea fart in
your tight little ass
it's too late I haven't went out to
steal [__] in a while
and besides all the skills I learned
from Pharaoh will be useless against him
he's the best of the best like Papa John
when it comes to Pizza
everything you just said except for the
Papa John stuff isn't true
what are you so afraid of that your
stupid siblings will think less of you
how can they think any more less of your
hand they do now
look at you soaking like a [__] while a
fat man is out there wearing the freshly
cleaned Whitey tighties on his huge
buttocks that belong to you
I say you go out there and snatch those
clothes back the night while he's asleep
show him what happens when you mess with
the maniac Marauder Manic the Hedgehog
hey do you know what you're right
I am a [__] Maniac I play games on
Roblox
okay
what's with the get up bro you look like
the burglar from The Sims 2.
I'll say it really is quite sexy if you
were just a tad bit fatter and you were
blue with a new Hawk I might have been
willing to motorboat those cheeks
oh it ain't nothing boys I'm just going
out thieving us all
thieving but bro I thought you kicked
that bad habit out of your life
if my more Sonia finds out about this
that's right and what about your job at
the laundromat you should be in bed your
boss won't be very pleased if you show
up late on your second day
yet who cares if you lost one delivery
let it go you wouldn't understand bro
this isn't about money or my job
this is about honor the honor among
Thieves this is what I have to do
I'm not losing my first job tonight not
a chance if Peril isn't going to pay me
then I have no other choice
but to take those clothes back to the
laundromat
but I can't just walk in otherwise
Pharaoh will see me my booty is so big
and he'll hear the Clapping of my cheeks
minutes before I arrive
aha not even Pharaoh would expect an
attack from above
Max is that you over there what the hell
are you doing out here
oh hi manic I didn't plan on running
into you tonight I'm just going to
murder feral and piss on his rotting
corpse because he stole a new pair of
socks from me
murder
Max we are thieves we don't kill people
wrong
you don't kill people because you're a
[__] who bows to the system
I just killed a family of four 36
minutes ago because I am a racist and
needed 50 more cents to buy a Crunchwrap
Supreme
but I thought you were religious
no I'm Max so what are you up to have
you come for blood red revenge against
feral as well
something like that
Hara knew it that [__] what
makes him think he can steal from his
own crew and get away with it that like
goes against what thieves stand for man
it's worse than being born a [__]
now now Max I'm sure there's a perfectly
reasonable explanation I'm talking
I knew it was bad news when feral moved
into town mainly because he lives in the
neighborhood just down the road and I'm
not talking about the chill section that
tend to be filled exclusively with white
people and a couple of Asians who
respectfully keep to themselves
I'm talking about the bad section of the
neighborhood with the blacks and
Mexicans
Max why are you so mean
I'm a ginger but enough about that check
out this radical toy I bought at Kmart
in the clearance section
no way is that one of those As Seen On
TV products
yeah but don't touch it it's drenched in
my slimy poopies
give me it
man I need to go to the bathroom I sure
hope no one steals my new pair of fluffy
socks
who dares to pinch the flat boot to your
feral the stink butt show yourself now
you better be a beautiful woman or I'm
going to sit upon your face with my
dirty butt
never mind it must have been my
imagination
stop it
well you got your socks back and feral
is still alive
originally I was going to take his life
tonight but you changed my mind because
if I go to jail I won't get to see you
fat ass again now bring it in bub you
want a hug but that's
what you're not afraid of anyone seeing
us are you come on it's getting cold
give your bro a tight squeeze and help
warm up his cinnamon buns
yeah that's the ticket bring it in tough
guy now go get your undies back
oh
[Music]
hahaha everyone look that stink bug guy
is taking a big steamy Duty in the Ally
way again someone getting a camera
is it wrong for a man to relieve himself
when he needs to
crows does he even have two ply toilet
paper to wipe himself
no you already know I don't so please
stop you're hurting my feelings
oh is that big time stick bug man going
to cry
I'm about to so can you go away now I
don't like people watching me take a
[__] I just wanna poopy your nasty man
don't you own the house to do that in
why don't you go buy one so we don't
have to see your crusty ass
I told you eight times I'm only doing
this here on the sidewalk because nobody
will hire me
do you know what it's like to be
diagnosed with depression and anxiety
do you think it's easy being a fat eight
foot tall stink bug on earth
when I used to live on an alien planet
called Mobius now I have to be here
where everyone else are sexy humans
do people laugh and berate you Dan and
day out just for how you look
no they don't they don't because you
look sexy
like a fried peanut butter and banana
sandwich with a side of deviled eggs and
a glass of milk
poor feral I never would have guessed he
had it so rough
here I thought he was just being mean
for the sick of it but I guess here on
Earth he doesn't have much of a choice
but to play the role of the bad guy
you know what screw you I've got clean
clothes waiting for me in the back alley
where are my clean clothes oh please
please God no
don't tell me another thief that if and
me stole my clothes again God why are
earthlings eat so much better than
Mobius
first I push my boy away and now this
[__]
just put a gun to my head already and in
this suffering
those were the only clean clothes I had
to cover my bare booty in the cool March
nights now I have to walk around town
with my oversized dick handball out
again
oh everyone is going to laugh at me
because of how my nights sag like an old
gym sock full of ripe oranges
foreign
[Music]
manic what are what are you doing here I
wasn't crying like a [__] [__] or
nothing
here my undies why do you have those
did you find the man who took them from
me good on you lied now turn around so I
can lick your ass
that won't be necessary feral actually
it was me I was the man that stole your
undies you but that can't be I stole
them from you first so they're mine
that's the rule among Thieves we steal
things from everyone else not from each
other that's what the Rat Patrol does do
I gotta beat your ass
forget about it what's done is done you
enjoy those warm fluffy clean clothes
feral
and don't come around the laundromat
again you hear me next time I won't be
as forgiving now get out of my sight
excuse me this is my poop stained out of
you [__]
you get out of my side with your green
bean looking ass
and if you try to steal the clothes that
I stole from you again I'm calling the
cops
[Music]
while manic I must say I am highly
disappointed in you I thought you would
have taken this job a little more
seriously not only did you lose the
clothes you were supposed to deliver but
you overslept as well I'm afraid I have
no choice but to fire you
I understand I'll get my things and head
out
hold that thought Mr Boss Man
feral up I mean Mr stranger what are you
doing here
manic would you care to explain to me
what's going on actually you did make
the delivery right on time
so you don't have to fire him
oh did he now
did I [__] stutter I literally just
said he did [__]
where's the [__] money
I'm sorry about that manic I guess I've
been a thief for so long
that I forgot certain things cost money
it's a tough world we are living in
that's for sure
now don't worry about it feral it's the
thought that counts
no it isn't that's only what people say
when they didn't get what they want
like when you ask your mom to get Papa
John's and she gets dominoes instead
but who cares about that the real reason
I came here is
cause I wanted to say that was some
mighty fine if work you did last night
you think so oh gosh it wasn't much and
I'm still Rusty
no way you swoop didn't and stole from
me right under my nose like I wasn't on
the wiser
only the best of the best could get away
with something like that you gotta tell
me how you did it
[Music]
sorry pops but if I tell you I gotta
tell everybody and I ain't about that
seems I really did take you well my boy
[Music]
I'm proud of you my boy truly not only
have you become a better Thief
you also became a better man
and I could only ever hope to become as
wonderful as you someday my boy
come on feral don't say such things in
public it's so embarrassing
[Music]
everywhere foreign
please help me
[Music]